to format them is to create a
их отформатировать то что сделать
counterbalance to Russia, one moment and the second
противовес России один момент а второй
moment they inflamed the nationalism
момент в них разожгли национализм
that they had in the campaign that Comrade
который походу у них был что товарищ
Stalin did not finish them in the fifty-
Сталин не дода вил их в пятьдесят
third year, and Comrade Khrushchev
третьем году-то там а товарищ Хрущёв это
smoothed it all out a little, but there it was necessary to
всё маленько сгладить а там надо было
see
видно жёстко
everything harshly Hello  Hello,
всё Здравствуйте Здравствуйте Вы
where are you from from the Southern Urals where are you
откуда я с Южного Урала вы откуда будете
from Rostov now I live in California 18
из Ростова сейчас живу в Калифорнии 18
years in 2 years will be the
лет через 2 года будет
twentieth Southern Urals - what
двадцатой Южный Урал - это что
exactly is the Southern Urals Chelyabinsk
именно Южный Урал это Челябинск
Magnitogorsk What city is
Магнитогорск Какой город
Magnitogorsk you are from
Магнитогорск сами из
Magnitogorsk Yes you are from Magnitogorsk What are
Магнитогорска Да сам с Магнитогорска А
you checking checking that  I have a
вы что проверяете проверяете что у меня
father from Mias, originally Mias, this is in
отец из миас родом миас есть это по
Chelyabinsk, this is in Chelyabinsk, well,
Челябинском это по Челябинском
yes, this is from there, this is from there, and
а а ну это да это отту это оттудова а
how do you communicate?
чём общаетесь
Yes Listen, with people, with everyone, I
Да Слушайте с людьми со всеми по-разному
put Ukraine differently, I thought about talking to people, I
поставил Украину думал с людьми
think about listening, they are
пообщаться думаю послушать они
aggressive, they are aggressive, I too
агрессивные они агрессивные Я вот тоже
I installed Ukraine and even installed a VPN to
ставил Украину и VPN даже ставил чтобы с
communicate with them, they see the American flag, they are
ними общаться видят американский флаг
so happy when I say that I come
такие довольные когда говорю что я родом
from Rostov, this is
из Ростова это
all a complete disgrace, yes,
всё разнос идёт полный да
I don’t know that they hate us, they do,
Я не знаю что они нас ненавидят они это
but the fact is that this one
а Да дело в том что этот самой их
raised them up, as I understand it  what do you know
приподняли Я так понимаю что знаете им
everyone owes them around I'm looking at them everyone
все должны вокруг Я Смотрю На Них им все
owes them around Russia the aggressor what
должны вокруг Россия агрессор то что
happened between us Before that there Until the twenty-
было между нами До этого там До двадцать
second year they all forgot it all there
второго года это всё забыли всё они там
how to say not they They they didn’t forget
все как сказать не они Они они не забыли
they with the Armed Forces remember they damn it tell  and
они с ВС помнят они блин рассказывают и
about this, that we took Crimea, that we
про это что мы Крым забрали что мы
Donetsk Lugansk In short, they are aggressive, they
Донецк Луганск Короче они агрессивные
remember everything. I also think that they forgot. It’s so
всё помнят Я тоже думаю что они забыли
simple, their Americans don’t.
Это так просто их амери не
No, it seems to me that they are just. Look,
Нет мне кажется что их просто Смотрите
the thing is that the Americans are pumping them up with
дело в том что их американцы накачивают
Anti-Russia, you know, because they are
Анти Россией понимаете потому что они
doing America  from Ukraine such Anti-
Америка делает из Украины такую Анти
Russia So the Ukrainians start
Россию Вот и украинцы они начинают
telling that it’s bad to live there in Russia,
рассказывать что в России там плохо жить
but in America it’s good America is
да А вот в Америке хорошо Америка
rich and so on So in short they
богатая и так дальше Вот они короче им
made a picture for them that America is
сделали картинку что Америка - это там
almost Heaven on earth and Russia is
чуть ли не Рай на земле а Россия - Это
hell  I don’t understand at all there in this
ад я я вообще не понимаю там же в этой
America, and what’s wrong is that you
Америке ну и то что пра правильно вы
say them correctly and you
говорите их и вы их
formatted them to
отформатировано их
format them as a counterweight to Russia one
отформатировать противовес России один
moment and the second moment they ignited
момент а второй момент в них разожгли
nationalism which
национализм который
Porin Goto Comrade Hv managed it a little and
порин гото товари Хв это малень сладил а
there it was necessary to be tough  This whole thing is that
там надо было видно жёстко всё это дело
in Russia we are
де нас у нас в России с национализмом
also tough with nationalism because when I was in
тоже жёстко потому что я я когда был в
Rostov Yes, I myself was a member of the Communist Party of the Russian Federation and
Ростове Да я сам в КПРФ был состоял и у
we did such patrols around the city
нас мы делали такие патрули по городу
because a lot of skinheads
потому что очень много скинхедов
got divorced and that’s
развелось
all the
э все
Meko of the Communist Party of the Russian Federation these in  Rostov, because I
ча Меко КПРФ эти в Ростове потому что я
live in California, they say that the
живу в Калифорнии то они говорят что
skinheads have disappeared Already and now their
скинхеды пропали Уже да что сейчас их
Caucasians In short, they were sweating stupidly if somewhere
кавказцы Короче тупо потели если где-то
they see them already there, Kadyrov apologizes
видят уже там они Кадырову извиняется
right away,
сразу
this is the head
это глав
speaking about these matters Well, listen, I think that
говоря этим делам Ну слушай я считаю что
this is just how to tell you it was  would
это просто как тебе сказать это было бы
probably be the trend of the times, probably
наверное веяние и времени наверное
most likely skinheads, then remember
скорее всего скинхеды потом вспоминай
all these youth movements there,
вот эти все молодёжные течения там
let’s say in our time there were punks there,
допустим в наше время панки были там
you know, in the nineties then the
знаешь это вот в девяностые годы тогда
punks were hippies Well, they are like hippies,
панки были хиппи были Ну хиппи они как
I see that now we have a trend in
так се я смотрю что сейчас течение в
Russia  left Akhmat strength that
России у нас осталось Ахмат сила что
like all the Chechens are afraid of the Chechens - these are the
типа все чеченцев боятся чеченцы - это
most important ones there against Kadyrov, no one will
самые главные там против Кадырова никто
say anything, just If someone
ничего не скажет вот просто Если кто-то
says it, he immediately apologizes
скажет сразу извиняется
Well, listen here, what is it, who is it?
Ну слушай здесь там что там кто там этот
I honestly haven’t encountered anything like this,
Я честно говоря с таким не сталкивался
for example, I don’t like it  Why
мне например мне не нравится Почему
say the Russians are the majority? We are
скажем русские - это большинство Мы же
the majority. But after all, there are
большинство Да всё-таки а чеченцев там
about a million Chechens in total. Yes,
какой-то их миллион населения всего Да
we defeated them then, and in short, and they
мы их победили тогда да короче и они
allow themselves to build us Russians. That’s what
себе позволяют строить нас русских вот
I can’t understand, how they, how we
это я не могу понять как они как мы
allowed this to happen.  they rule us Well,
допустили тому что они нами управляют
I won’t say that they rule,
Ну я не скажу что они управляют
you know, the fact is that in any
понимаешь Дело в том что они в любом
case, they are also on a
случае они также
par with the Russians, also in the same
наравне с русскими также на той же
Ukraine, they fight shoulder to shoulder with us, what do
Украине плечо о плечо бьются с нами что
we have here, look here It’s not quite like that,
тут у нас смотри тут Тут не совсем так
look what they are doing U  I have
смотри что они делают У меня же у меня
an acquaintance and a classmate, yes, he is an Airborne Forcesman and
знакомый да одноклассник да он ВДВшник и
he says, in short, they created there in
он говорит они короче сделали там в
Chechnya, there in Gudermes, like a
Чечне там в Гудермесе типа Академию
Special Forces Academy, and so on they are
спецназа и так дальше они набирают вот
recruiting this Akhmat regiment. Yes, they are recruiting. These are not
этот полк Ахмат Да набирают Это же не
Chechens in the Akhmat regiment. I also thought that
чеченцы в полк Ахмат Я тоже думал что
Akhmat is  Chechens are howling There are no Chechens
Ахмат - это чеченцы воют Нет там чеченцы
in the leadership And so they recruit
в руководстве А так они набирают на
Russian guys from different
контракты русских парней из разных
regions for contracts and throw them into a meat grinder,
регионов и бросают их короче в мясорубку
you know, and they hang medals for themselves like Akhmat,
понимаешь а медальки себе типа ахмату
in short, you know what’s the joke That
короче вешают понимаешь в чём прикол То
is, these are not Chechens of the
есть это не чеченцы
regiment, but Wagner
полке а Вагнер
Wagner is not Wagner, this is Russian  no Well, what
Вагнер не Вагнер это рус же не Ну какая
difference does it
разница что с
make what they did to you?
ва что с пригож сделали Да
Well, some of them went to the army, some of them left,
ну часть ушла в армию часть ушла они
some of them left for the great Russian
часть ушла за при при великий русский
man, the combat units remained Prigozhin was the
чело боевые части остались Пригожин был
only Hope of Russia, you
это единственная Надежда России
know, here's a Russian
понимаешь Вот русский
man,
чело
listen, there was a great Russian man
Слушай прин был великий русский человек
before  until he raised the
до того как пока он не поднял
same understanding I don’t want to say anything I
теж понима Я ничего не хочу сказать Я
even thought that Prigozhin should be made
даже я Даже думал что пригожина сделать
president Here he is Look look
президентом Вот он Смотри посмотри
Now now they’re putting all these people in
Сейчас же сейчас садят всех этих кто
prison
короче Да министерское тот в
she steals where the shells they built
эгу она ворует где снаряды они строили
palaces and dachas for themselves while the Russian guys
себе дворцы дачи пока русские ребята
were dying Well, what’s wrong
погибали Ну что не так
Listen well on that on that no wait it
Слушай ну на тот на тот нет подожди оно
was like that but at that moment at that moment
было так но на тот момент на тот момент
I think it was impossible, you know, to suddenly
я считаю нельзя было знаешь резко всё
break everything over the knee Well, it’s impossible If
через колено ломать Ну как нельзя Если
if  Russian people were not given shells to them,
если им снаряды не давали русских людей
in short, they were allowed to carry out meat assaults, as much as
пускали короче на мясные штурмы сколько
he said, uh, I have a friend in Wagner, in
он говорил э у меня знакомый в вагнере
short, yes, he was left without a leg,
есть короче да он без ноги остался
he says, he says we are only on bakhmut,
говорит он говорит нас только на бахмуте
in short, Prigozhin then announce 20,000
короче Пригожин то оглашать 20.000
dead And so he says there are thirty to
погибших А так говорит там тридцатка
eat, they just put it in meat, you know
есть просто мясом положили понимаете
bom No this is well here you understand one thing here is a
бом Нет это ну здесь ты Пойми одно здесь
nuclear bomb AF the rest AF This is
ядерная бомба ВС остальное ВС Это потому
because because the Americans stupidly they
что потому что американцы тупо они
told Putin in short Don’t you dare don’t you dare and
сказали Путину короче Не смей не смей и
that’s it and Putin listens to them you know Putin
всё и Путин слушается их понимаешь Путин
is afraid of America that’s the problem in the World Cup but
боится Америку вот в ЧМ проблема
lately there’s been a trend
этом пото последнее время тенденция
like this look  the sax that was collected in
такая посмотри сакс который собрали в
Kazan, pay attention to this
Казани обрати на это
that America is gnashing its teeth, that
внимание что Америка зубами скрежета что
England is gnashing its teeth, everyone
Англия зубами скрита все
else there is pretty serious there 2
остальные там довольно-таки серьёз там 2
in the markets And that's all And what is the result of
по базари И всё И что что результат
Brix someone refused the dollar to everyone in
Брикс кто-то отказался от доллара всем
Russia I understand how what what Brix is ​​so No
России понима как что что Брикс так Нет
well no no well you Well no look America is
ну нет нет ну ты Ну нет смотри Америка
clever America is pressing with sanctions now
хитро Америка давит санкциями теперь вот
in Russia that’s what my mother in Rostov
в России вот что у меня мама в Ростове
says that butter
говорит что сливочное масло короче
has risen in price because in Russia there is
подорожало потому что в России
no butter now the Arabs
сливочного масла нет теперь вон арабы
will bring us butter and what
будут завозить нам сливочное масло и
yes What what  where did you get the
что да Чего чего вы откуда вы взяли что
idea that there is no butter in Russia
в России сливочного масла нет пому
because Putin didn’t agree that
потому что Путин е договорился чтобы
butter should be imported look Novo
сливочное масло ввозили посмотри Ново
how zha how Belarusian it’s all from where
как жа как Белорусская всё оно откуда
where do you get it from I don’t
откуда вы это берёте я не
look about butter Yes nothing
посмотри про сливочное масло Да ниче их
look at them I myself I myself I live myself  in Russia,
смотреть я сам я сам Я сам живу в России
but why should I watch
но зачем мне смотреть
about the World Cup? What kind of butter is
про о ЧМ вы вообще какое сливочное масло
this? They are breaking records. They turned to the Arab
это бьют рекорды обратились в арабски
Emirates for importing butter to
Эмираты за импорт сливочного масло чтоб
bring down the price a little. Yes, Russia started
сбить немножко цену Да вот Россия начала
begging for butter from Turkey,
выпрашивать сливочное масло у Турции ну
damn, well, this is real, what is it?
блин ну это реально ну что раска это
Look, I understand  Well, they
Смотри я понимаю ну это эти они
do this on purpose so that in short, then they
специально делают чтобы короче потом
give us these legs again, you know.
снова нам давать эти окорочка понимаешь
But they send chicken legs, beads legs, so
Бут куриные окорочка ножки буса
that we are happy, you know,
присылать чтобы мы радовались понимаешь
well, there was no. Listen, no one
ну был был нет Слушай это никто не
denies that there were legs. Well, I’ll say this,
отрицает были ножки Ну я скажу так вот у
they have legs here in California.
них тут тут окорочка у них в Калифорнии
very tasty, I like it, it’s
очень вкусный мне нравится это это
normal, yes, and do you now sell
нормаль да А у вас сейчас продают ихние
their chicken legs or not? Yes, what kind of chicken do we have?
своей курицы тьма тьмущая своей свинины
eggs
яйцами Да там не было кризиса с яйцами
There, people just decided to make extra money and
Там просто люди решили подзаработать и
they all Slow down the shipment of eggs and that’s
всё они Притормози отгрузку яиц и всё
it So now eggs have become more expensive, they are imported
Так теперь яйца подорожали их завозят
from somewhere Yes, how they have become more expensive Look,
откуда-то Да ну как они подорожали Вон
they are 80 rubles please
они 80 руб пожалуйста
de small
де мелкие
ta1 No, there is C1
та1 Нет там есть C1
there, well, that’s In short, here in
есть там ну это Короче у нас в
California Yes  these are African Americans
Калифорнии Да это вот это афроамериканцы
Only the poor eat, in short, those who
Только едят бедные короче которые на
live on welfare C1 I and in m
пособие живут C1 я а в м
difference in
разни
dietary importance the idea is that the
диетической важности идея в том что
chicken is a chicken that lacks
курка курица которой не хватает
vitamins Yes and she cannot lay a
витаминов Да и она не может снести
normal
нормальное
egg it is small it does
яйцо оно маленькое оно у неё получается
not form completely Yes no no  so
не формируется полностью Да не не так
small when the eggs the eggs the chicken eggs
маленько когда яйца яйца яйца курицы
are laying there is an ordinary convey and it’s
несут идёт обыкновенный конве и идёт
just
просто
packaging correctly Well why look a
расфасовка правильно Ну почему смотри
normal healthy chicken she doesn’t lay a
нормальная здоровая курица она не несёт
small egg she no but yes yes no yes Yes
маленькое яйцо она нет бо да да не да Да
no they are all the same chickens sitting all
нет они все одинаковы курицы сидят все
together sitting what are you telling me
вместе сидят что ты мне рассказываешь
In short no  enough and because the farms
Короче не хватает и потому что фермы
feed shorter and give little compound feed,
кормят короче и малое комбикорма дают
that's all because there is not enough
вот и всё потому что не хватает
compound feed. Well, yes, everything is enough, that is,
комбикормов Ну да да всё хватает то есть
look at what. Here's an egg from my grandmother in short,
посмотри Какое Вот яйцо у бабушки короче
in the village, this is the egg you know like this.
в деревне вот такое яйцо понимаешь такое
We had a problem with chicken,
Как уста нам проблема была с курятиной
but it's the same
но её же
no So you have there, damn, what’s shorter
нет Так у вас там блин что там короче
already And how much is the pension in Russia now,
уже А сколько сейчас пенсия в России
how much is the minimum pension in Russia? Yes,
сколько пенсия в России минимальная Да
no, well, listen, to be honest, I don’t know Well,
нет ну слушай честно говоря не знаю Ну
000 is probably 25
000 наверное 25
minimum Yes yes It can’t be, well,
минимальная Да да Не может быть а ну
now I’ll look at my place Mom, I have
сейчас посмотрю у меня У ма у меня у
mothers 17 I think
мамки 17 по-моему
honestly Well, listen, well, what does the minimum pension have to do with it?
чесно Ну Ну слушай ну а А причём здесь
Here you are for the minimum
пенсия минимальная Вот ты за минимальная
pension in Russia 11.8 186 rubles in short 12
пенсия в России 11.8 186 руб короче 12
less than 12,000 the minimum pension is 120
меньше 12.000 минимальная пенсия это 120
dollars Well listen,
долла Ну слушай
wait with us, these
подожди у нас у нас вот эти
African Americans receive more benefits at
афроамериканцы получают больше пособия в
If you don’t mind, it turns out that Russian
раз не против поди получается русские
grandmothers are now surviving on 12,000
бабушки сейчас выживают на 12000
rubles
руб
Dinna 250 dollars is Nin’s beggarly pension is
динне 250 дол это Нин нищенская пенсия
just
просто
tough Wait with you Wait wait wait
жесть Подожди у тебя Подожди подожди
wait with you Internet How much does the
подожди у тебя интернет Сколько стоит
Internet cost for me 5 dollars a
интернет у меня 5 долларов в
month 5 dollars a month mobile communication
месяц 5 долларов в месяц мобильная связь
how much is this included and mobile  The connection
сколько это входит и мобильная связь у
we have in the kit
нас в комплекте
is what you whistle. Yesterday I
идёт это что ты свистишь Я вчера с
talked to an American. He
американцем разговаривал у него 40
only costs 40 dollars for the Internet and 8
долларов только интернет стоит и 8
dollars for mobile communications. He probably does
долларов мобильная связь Это он наверное
n’t know, he’s calling somewhere, in short, to Russia
не знаю куда-то звонит короче в Россию
on a mobile phone, where is he calling in Russia, where is
по мобильно куда он в Россию звонит куда
he calling in Russia?  calls if a person lives
он в Россию звонит если человек живёт у
there, it’s a kinship, what are you telling me,
себя там это родстве что ты мне рассказы
look at 5 dollars In short, we have a tariff
смотри 5 долларов Короче у нас это тариф
like A 10 dollars is a family package
типа а 10 долларов - это семейный пакет
Listen, if I have a salary like an
Слушай если у меня зарплата как у
anthropology teacher, 9,000
преподавателя антропологии 9.000
dollars 900,000 rubles, you can damn it and
долларов 900.000 руб можно блин и
pay for the Internet and go ahead  you're
интернет платить и ходи что ты мне
telling me no need to me I lived in Rostov
рассказываешь не надо мне я в Ростове
I lived in Rostov I lived here
жил Я те я жил в Ростове я жил тут у
I have something to compare you in short about
меня есть что сравнить ты короче про
some expensive ones with How much is your
какие-то дорогие эти с За сколько у тебя
salary I have about 70,700
зарплата у меня порядка 70 700
dollars 7 ssia Well 700 dollars is that
долларов 7 сся Ну 700 долла это меньше
Homeless
чем у нас получают бездомные
African-Americans receive less help than ours Well,
афроамериканцы помощь Ну хорошо
great, let them live with you
замечательно Пусть они у тебя
What kind of car do you have
живут те Какая у тебя
in the sense of nyah
машина в смысле ня
Lada
Лада
Granta is funny, I just don’t understand Lada
Гранта смешного-то я не пойма никак Лада
Granta from Putin is the
Гранта от Путина
guarantor You can even kill yourself on it
гаранта Ты даже на ней убиться можно
Lada
Лада
Granta I am the
Гранта Я же
one  no no sense Why should I have a car ko
го не не смысл Зачем мне иметь машину ко
How much does Grant's cutting cost a
Сколько стоит сеча Гранта
new Yes I have no idea how much it
новая Да Понятия не имею сколько она
costs wait I understood everything you're a chain opener or something like that
стоит подожди я всё понял ты цепник что
Yes I p you just
ли очередной Да я п ты настолько только
now realized that I'm a chain opener people
сейчас понял что я цеп сошник народ
look he's so intellectually
смотрите он настолько интеллектуально
limited only when with  him is already
ограничены только когда с него уже
open
открыт
for respect vy potrno alarm you
для увага вй потрно тревоги ты
come on I thought he would
давай я думал он ещё на сирене
burn the Lada Granta with the siren the dream of an emigrant
спалит Лада Гранта мечта эмигранта
subscribe to my Ista I don’t know why
подпишись на мий Иста Я не знаю для чего
this is for what there is to marvel at oh
це те Для чего то там дивитись на ой
face Ale for you one two or three clicks
фейс Але для тебе один два або три клика
and Ale  ti trimae mene and I will be kasati Wow
а Але ти тримае мене и я буду казати Вау
in me there Kupa folov and in mene will be a
в мене там Купа фолов и в мене буде
classy mood to robiti Novi cool
класний настрий щоб робити Нови крути
video subscribe to my Instagram popk
видео подпишись на мий Instagram попк
Andriy like
Андрий вот
this let me
так давай я тебя
check for you H
чекаю H